As Mayor, it is my
deeply tedious pleasure
to kick off the 83rd or 84th
Annual E-Waste Recycling Festival!
Down in front!
Sorry.
I get aroused in crowds.
I will now throw out
the ceremonial first dump,
this old,
inefficient vote-rigger!
These old doomsday devices
are dangerously unstable.
I'll rest easier not
knowing where they are.
So long, overly complicated Japanese toilet.
Please, not to throw away. I
give you a happy poopie time.
Sorry,
you know too much.
Seems like a good place
to ditch some evidence.
Flexo?
What are you doing
in a hazardous-waste bin?
Haven't you heard?
Us bending units
are dangerously outdated.
We overheat, we're radioactive,
we cause erectile...
Who were you talking to?
No one. Your mama.
Shut up. Take your pick.
Scoop Chang,
New New York Times
online podcast
blog comments editor.
Mr. Mayor, isn't this
e- waste dangerous?
Not at all, Scoop.
Not after it's hauled off to the
third world by an expendable team
of minimum-wage nobodies.
Good news, nobodies!
Greetings, my friends!
It shan't take long
to strip down your clunker.
There's nothing wrong
with our clunker.
Really? Because we can smelt
out the deadly, deadly chromium
to make rat poison
and artificial sweeteners.
No, thanks.
We're delivering e-waste.
Pity.
We're halfway done.
This thing is 40% chromium!
Gentle now. Gentle with
the hover dumpster.
Ready for processing!
What smells like
bloody sinuses?
We burn your e-waste down
to the usable metals,
safely releasing the toxins
into our air and drinking water.
That's the
worst thing I've ever seen!
Really?
Then don't look over there.
Whee!
Okay, kids.
Let's play "find the shiny".
That's even more horrific! Is
all the work done by children?
No, not the whipping.
Granted, we later learned some
positive things about recycling,
but a better solution
is to use our electronics
as long as possible instead of
throwing them out in the first place.
I'm gonna start by keeping my old
cell phone, even if it is outdated.
Hello, Miss Turanga. Your call
to St. Louis has gone through.
Well, let's at least
throw this TV out.
The batteries in the remote
are getting low.
No! Put that back
and turn it on!
I was just trying
to help.
More on this
breaking puff piece
after a word
from our sponsor.
With the new eyePhone,
you can watch, listen,
ignore your friends,
stalk your ex,
download porno
on a crowded bus,
even check your e-mail
while getting hit by a train.
All with the new eyePhone.
From Mom.
A new eyePhone?
Forget this junk.
Well, this is a fine
how-do-you-do!
So long!
Sayonara.
Bye-bye!
Good riddance!
Yup!
Toodle-oo.
Come on, let's buy some eyePhones online.
Wait. I thought we were
buying our eyePhones online.
We are on line.
But I thought the Mom Store was across town.
It is across town.
But I thought...
Stop thinking, Fry!
I feel like
a mindless zombie.
I wish I knew how long
we've been waiting.
The eyePhone has
an app for that!
Is there an app for kissing my shiny metal ass?
Several!
Ooh!
No, the light!
I guess I'm off to hell.
That's the store, Professor.
Wow! It's that
obscure underground song
that's constantly
playing everywhere.
Hello, dearies.
Welcome to the Mom Store.
The new eyePhones are in short
supply, so please form an orderly...
Out of the way!
I need...
Move!
Are there any left?
There may be one.
Okay, it's $500, you have no choice of carrier,
the battery can't
hold a charge
and the reception
isn't very...
Shut up and take my money!
The new eyePhone
is wonderful.
I use it to check recipes
and send threatening e-mails
to unauthorized
third-party app developers.
Say, you're from one of those
ethnicities that knows about technology.
Why is it called
an eyePhone?
I'll explain
after I install it.
Neat.
Now for the earpiece.
But my favorite app
is called Twitcher.
Twitcher lets you
send and receive
short messages or videos
called twits.
Why, here's a twit now.
Hi, Mom.
I love you more than...
Low battery.
But don't take
my word for it.
Unbiased-Reviews.mom says
Twitcher is the killer app.
And when I say killer app,
I mean killer app!
Ow!
And now,
another downloadisode
of The Real
Housewives of Sim City.
She needs to reset.
I'll say it to her face.
No wonder
traditional media is dead.
Check out this
webisode of Hypnotoad.
Enjoy your outdated format,
Grandpa.
Nowadays, cool kids like me
mash up our own phone-isodes.
It's from the kidnappers.
My nephew is alive!
And he's in this envelope.
They cut off one
of my dimensions!
No! No!
Oh, my God, it's Bender!
He'll save us!
What's happening to me?
Is it puberty?
It's a phone call, dingus.
These eyePhones
are phones, too?
Duh!
Fry-lo.
Hi, Fry.
Did you know these eyePhones
are phones, too?
Duh! Hey, is it safe to
talk while you're flying?
Oh, totally.
This thing's hands-free.
That's how I can eat this taco and this spaghetti.
I'm hanging up now.
Hey, check out this Internet video
of some idiot crashing her spaceship!
You recorded that?
The eyePhone
records everything.
All I did was add
a laugh track
and twit it to my
10,000 followers.
That reminds me. It's time
to twit my hourly twupdate.
What's up, followers?
Fry here.
Burping eggs, scratching my underarm fungus,
looking for love.
Send.
Underarm fungus?
Too much information.
It's exactly the right
amount of information!
For years, I've collected personal
data with old-fashioned methods,
like spybots
and info-squitos.
This guy sure loves porno.
But now,
thanks to Twitcher,
morons voluntarily spew out every
fact I need to exploit them!
Target acquired, Mother.
Fire direct
marketing algorithm!
Do you suffer from
the heartbreak of...
My underarm fungus.
Then you, Mr. or Mrs... need the soothing relief
of Mom's Caustic
Anti-Fungal Bleach!
Can I somehow charge it to my
eyePhone for an additional fee?
Hell, yes!
Hey, fatso,
stuffa you face!
This thing always seems to
know when I got the munchies!
Attention, followers.
It's free topping day at the pizza
place across the street! Send.
Duh! That's why we all came
over here for lunch. Send.
Greetings, followers.
This is day five of my solo kayak
journey around the world. Send.
Can you believe 50,000 idiots
swallow that crap? Send.
Oops.
Wait. You have 50,000 followers
? I only have three. Send.
I unsubscribed yesterday.
I got the most followers 'cause
I give the people what they want.
Like this video of you doing
karate in your underpants.
Help! Police!
Send.
That is low, Bender,
even by your standards.
My what now?
Since when is the Internet about
robbing people of their privacy?
August 6, 1991.
I'll bet I can get
as many followers as you
without sinking
to your level.
What do you say? First one to
a million followers wins a buck.
You're on!
Send.
What happens to the loser?
Let's make it interesting.
Why is Mr. Chunks doing that?
Because the loser of our bet
has to do a double somersault
into a tub of
alien goat vomit.
Wait, let's make it
interestinger.
Vomit and diarrhea.
Good idea. That way
we don't waste an end.
It's putrid.
What do you feed him?
What comes out one end,
we feed to the other.
Also Indian food.
Let the contest begin!
Amazing.
Some dumb bastard
has nearly a million other dumb
bastards following his every twit!
Are you dumb bastards listening
to me, you dumb bastards?
Why are you
so angry, Mommy?
Oh, I'm sorry.
I guess I'm just a little
nervous about my evil plan.
You dumb bastards!
You see, the plan is about to enter phase two.
As soon as someone
reaches a million followers,
I'll use them to transmit
the twit-worm.
Mother, you devious hag. Tell
us more about this twit-worm.
It's a very special
computer virus,
for instead of
infecting computers,
it infects
the human brain.
I like it.
The million followers will
become an army of zombies
eager to obey
my every command!
The important thing is,
we're a family.
No, it's not!
Ew! He sneezed in it.
Oh, God,
I'm going to lose the bet.
I'm gonna have to swim in the
juice of the Puke-Me-Poop-You.
Don't give up. You just
need more titillating twits.
Trust me,
I want twits that tittle.
Then you're gonna have to sink to Bender's level.
Stop acting like
the Queen of England.
Who's that?
The Queen of England?
Excuse me.
I have to... Someplace.
That was odd. Where'd that singing come from?
It wasn't the goat. All
of its orifices are in use.
I dreamed
a dream in time gone by
When hope was high
and life worth living
I dreamed that
love would never die
I dreamed that God
would be forgiving
What the hell is that?
Nothing.
I'm not nothing.
All my life,
everyone's called me nothing.
You have a boil on your butt
that sings show tunes with you?
Don't look at me.
I'm a freak.
No, no, well...
I've been ashamed of Susan
as long as I can remember.
You named your boil Susan?
A boil kinna have a name? They
also said a boil kinna sing, but...
Amazing grace
How...
Ew! She's Scottish.
I lance her every few months,
but she always grows back.
It's hard enough
being a Cyclops,
but if anyone found out about
Susan, I'd be devastated.
Amazing grace
How...
Whoa! Gross.
Million-follower gross.
Fry, delete that.
Delete that right now!
What? Oh. Okay.
So much for
a pleasant swim in vomit.
Send.
Did you delete it?
Uh...
Thanks, Fry,
you're a good friend.
Amazing grace
How...
Hey, there she goes
in the genuine.
Let's get to hooting.
Whoa, whoa, whoa!
If it ain'ts the world's
number ones Internet sensation.
Where? Also, what?
Amazing grace...
How...
Play it one more time.
No!
It's humiliating and degrading
to Leela. Play it 10 more times.
I know I shouldn't
have twitted that,
but not swimming in barf
might ease my conscience.
But if Leela should find out,
her dignity sac will rupture.
That's why we can't
let her see this.
Leela, lock the door
so Leela doesn't...
How could you do this?
Poor Mr. Chunks. At least
he died doing what he loved.
He's in a better place now.
There, I turned a regular
board into a diving board.
Impending news, everyone.
We're about to learn
the winner of the bet.
Oh, boy, oh, boy,
oh, boy.
I hope it's me.
Wait a minute. There's a chance I could lose?
That wasn't
part of the deal.
Sweet Georgia Brown of Kingston Town. It's a tie.
Since no one lost,
no one has to jump.
All right, a tie!
I win again!
I'm a scuzzball.
Don't feel bad.
At least you're not Leela.
A tie?
This worked out better
than I could have hoped.
Now I'll have two
million zombies.
Actually, Fry and Bender may
share some of the same followers.
All we can say
for sure is that
there will be between one
million and two million zombies.
All I can say
for sure is...
Now, stop getting slapped
and power up the twit-worm!
It's both disgusting and
inspiring, like Jared from Subway.
Okay, I'm a freak
with a singing butt boil,
but I'm still a human being,
more or less.
Singing butts boil?
That's yesterdays's news.
Like that giant caterpillar
what ate Jared from Subway.
Nows us Internet geeks gots
a whole new video sensation.
So, my humiliation
is over?
Who are you?
And now, to create
an unstoppable army
of between one and two
million zombies!
Shouldn't you wait for the weather to clear up?
No. I give you
the twit-worm!
Send.
I'm sick of my head
doing things.
Leela!
Fry,
I came to talk to you.
No,
It looked like you were just
sitting there, but whatever.
I am so, so sorry
for what I did,
and I know I can never
make it up to you.
You don't have to apologize.
In fact, I came to thank you.
I think you mean hit me.
Everyone knows my secret,
but no one cares.
I have nothing
to hide anymore.
Fry, thanks to
your selfish rudeness,
a terrible weight has been
lifted from my heart.
That's not the only place you
need a terrible weight lifted.
Susan and I are agreed.
For the first time in our lives,
we're not ashamed of who we are.
I was never ashamed.
Come here.
What stinks? Were you
rolling around in New Jersey?
Leela, I knew I could
never make it up to you,
so I did the next best thing.
I put myself through the same
humiliation I put you through.
Aw. You didn't
have to do that.
I didn't? Damn.
Don't worry. By tomorrow,
no one will remember.
Can I have another hug?
No.
Hold your nose
and give it a go.
Introducing
the all-new eyePhone 2.0.
Dumb bastards.